Edited at https://subtitletools.com
You are one of the Seafolk, correct?
しん力ヽいぞ<
ジェノス深海族というのは お前力ヽ?
What if I am?
あなた また新しい兵隊さん?
You must be another soldier—
I am here to eliminate you.
ジ工 ノ ス お前を排除萱る
ジ 工 ノ ス 敵は今ので最後なのガ ?
Was that the last of them?
Wow!
Amazing!
They must have been desperate.
ジ工ノス
<よほどの危機だったようだな>
うりやあ!
一同 うわつ
キレたわ
Now I'm angry.
I'll tear you to shreds.
グチヤグチヤにし亡あげる
また油断…
I let my guard down again.
I never learn.
俺も学習が下手だな
Saitama...
ヒゲ職員 サイタマ…
You're rank 2 of the C Class.
ヒゲ職員 C級2位のキ三もやる気力`?
Are you sure?
あ
マ
夕
イ
柑
Yeah.
Hurry it up. It's raining.
雨降つ亡る力`ら早 し亡れ
He burst through every record
during the fitness exam...
ヒゲ 職員
体力試験で新記録を連発>一
And he worked with some S-class
heroes to destroy that meteor.
S級と協力し亡
隕石を破壊した功績>一
いんせき
だ力ヾ その素性が不明なため
インチキだと噂されている>一
But, because he came out of nowhere,
some people are saying he's a fraud.
Any other C-class hero I'd stop...
本来ならC級は止めるベきだが…
This may be our chance
to see how strong he truly is.
メガネ職員
今回 彼の真価を見極めることが
できる力ヽもしれない
サイ タマ君 今力ヽら指示曹る現場へ
急行し亡くれ
Saitama, here's the location.
Head there immediately.
ライダ一ハア ハア ハア…
む無
UNYIELDING JUSTICE
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
Veni, vidi, vici!
I can't stand it
But I won't stop
One punch, one victory, rinse and repeat
I win, all the time, no exceptions
Power, get power
Until it isn't possible anymore
Hero
I don't want applause
or people singing my praises
Hero
That's why I fight evil away from prying eyes
Nobody knows who he is
Enemies darken the skies
But I won't turn and flee
Hero
I fight because I decided
I would never back down
A solitary hero
I wanna be a superhero
シ工丿しタ一力ヽら逃げ出せる者は
今曹ぐ行け!
Those who can walk, leave the shelter now!
俺が勝亡るとは限らない
I cannot promise I will win.
Run, while I keep him busy!
奴の相手を し亡いるうちに急げ !
一同 うわあ~ !
None of you monkeys will escape me!
ー匹もおおおお逃がさなああああい!
ああつ!
あう!一
うわ!一
Lightning Eye!
らいこうがん
雷光眼 !
目カヾ...
I can't see...
Machinegun Blows!
ジ工 ノス マシンガンブ口一 !
You do like combo attacks, don't you?
ほんとに連打好きね
一同 わあ !
力ヾ・ がんばれ お兄ちやん!
You can do it!
Quiet!
うるさい!
Now you melt, girl.
深海王 ガキは溶けてなさい
ジ工ノスはつ は… ああつ…
深海王 ふふふふふ〟.
Lヽーえいつ !
いえ一い はつ !
あなたー 人なら… えい ! _
If you'd focused on me,
you could have easily dodged my little ball of acid.
あんな溶解液かわ曹くらい
箇単だったでしょうに
まさ力ヽガキを力ヽばって
自滅曹るなん亡ね一
Instead, you chose to sacrifice yourself to save a runt.
You're a fool, but I give you credit for giving me a few scratches.
あなた バ力だけど一
私に軽傷を負わせたことは
評価曹るわ
Of course, they've already healed.
もう治つたけどね
Now, die.
死になさい
Justice Crash!
無免ライダ一
ジヤステイスクラツシユ !
ああん?
無免ライダ一
正義の自転車乗り 無免ライダ一参上!
むめん
The Cyclist for Justice,
Licenseless Rider is here!
ジ工ノス
C級ランキング 卜ツプの?>
The highest ranked C-class hero?
D-Don't...
It's Licenseless Rider!
男性ー 無免ライダ一だ
男性 2  無免ライダ一が来亡れた
Licenseless Rider came for us.
But he...
男性3でも…
I'm bored already.
もう飽きたのよ
おりやああ!
無免ライダ一ああつ
あ ごめんね
卜ドメさ曹の遅れちゃっ亡
Oh, my apologies.
I nearly forgot to kill you.
Justice Tackle...
無免ライダ一
ジヤステイスタツク丿し…一
期待され亡ないのは…
No one expects much—
深海王 ああ ! ?
分力`つ亡るんだ…
...from me.
They think a C-class hero
won't be much help.
C級ヒ一口一が
大し亡役に立たないなん亡こと一
I know that better than anyone!
俺が一番分力`つ亡るんだ !
I'm not good enough
to advance to B-class status.
俺じや巳級で通用しない一
I'm weak. I know that much.
自分が弱いってことは
ちゃんと分力ヽってるんだ
俺がお前に勝てないなん亡ことは
No one has to tell me I have
no chance of beating you.
I already know that!
俺が一番よ分力`つてるんだよおツ ・・・ !
What are you babbling about?
な~にボソボソほざい亡るの?
命乞い?
Begging for your life?
And yet, I must try.
無免ライダ一
それでもやるし力ヽないんだ
勝亡る勝てないじやな ! _
It's not about winning or losing!
It's about me taking you on
right here, right now!
ここで俺は お前に
立ち向力ヽわなくちゃいけないんだ!
わけ分力ヽんないこと言つ亡ないで
早<<たばりなさい
Enough of your rambling.
Time to finish you off.
You can do it!
壬 少年 頑張れ ! 一
壬無免ライダ一 頑張れええ !
Licenseless Rider, you can do it!
You're the Cyclist for Justice!
自転車のお兄ちゃん 頑張れえええ ! 一
Beat that weird monster, beat him!
深海族なん力` やつつけちやえ !
You can do it!
頑張れええええええ !
そ うだ 頑張れ
Yeah, get him!
Beat him up!
母親そいつをやつつけ亡 !
We're counting on you, Licenseless Rider!
あんたが頼りなんだよ 無免ライダ一
You can do it!
男性4頑張つてくれ
男性5勝つてくれ!
Beat him!
Good luck!
女性 頑張れ !
無免ライダ一 ぬうおおおおおあああああ !
無駄でしたあV
I think not!
無免ライダ一 うつ
You did fine.
サイ夕マ
よ<やつた ナイスファイ卜
Nice fight.
ん? ま~たまたゴ三が
しゃしゃり出亡きたわね
Yet another piece of garbage
washed up on my shore?
あ あ・ おい ジ工ノス?一
H-Hey, Genos!
Are you still alive?!
おま… 生き亡んの力` それ?
Master...
ま ちよつと待つ亡ろ
Hang on for a second.
I've gotta pound this Seafreak
or whatever it's called.
今 チン力イ族とやらを
ぶつ飛ば曹力ヽらな
I heard that!
聞こえ亡るのよ !
ん? へえ あなた 私の殴打で
倒れないなんて やるわね
Impressive.
You're still on your feet
after one of my punches.
Clearly you're different
from the rest of this trash.
今までのゴ三とは
明ら力ヽに違うわ
なあに テメ一のパンチが
貧弱曹ぎるだけだろ?
Huh? Your punch was too weak, that's all.
男性ーまた誰力ヽ現れたぞ
誰だ あれ? ヒ一ロ一?
Hey, someone else is over there.
Who is that?
A hero?
That head...
男性2 あの頭…
ヒ 一 口 一名簿で見た気が萱る
I remember it from the Hero Registry.
I know him!
俺 知つてる C級の新人だよ
He's a C-class rookie.
I think he's rank 2.
確力`ランキング2位の
C級力ヽ・‥
C-class?
So we're still gonna get killed...
絶望的な状況は変わらないんだな
But that punch didn't hurt him at all.
でも さつき殴られたように見えたわ
That's your imagination.
男性ー 見間違いだろ一
あいつのパンチで何人もヒ一ロ一が
吹き飛ばされたの 見亡ただろ?
You saw how many heroes were blown
away by that thing's punches, right?
私は深海の王 海の王
I am the King of the Deep,
Lord of the Seas.
All life on Earth comes from the sea,
as if she were our mother.
海は万物の源であり
母親のようなもの一
In other words, as ruler of the seas,
つま り海の支配者である私は
I am at the top of a pyramid that includes
every living organism in this world!
世界中 全生態系ビラ三ッ ドの
頂点に立つ存在であるということ
その私に 楯突いたとぃう〟・
To defy me, means—
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
サイ夕マ
うんうん 分力ヽつた分力ヽつた
It's raining out, so let's do this.
雨降つ亡る力`ら 早力`力`つ亡こい
深海王 でやあああ !
What?!
人々 ええええええ‥
Awesome!
That was amazing!
母親ああ ` ~
やつた! つ よ力つた!
Thank goodness!
He did it!
人々 萱げ~ !
サイ夕マはあ… つまんね一な一
Well, that was lame.
今回は少し期待したんだけどな
I kinda had my hopes up, too.
I'm back with my weapons.
ソ二ツク
急いで装備を整え亡来たんだがな一
しん力ヽいおう
ふんつ 深海王め 逃げられた力ヽ
But damn you, Deep Sea King.
You got away.
あ 何だ ありや?
Hey, what's that?
ジ工 ノ ス 郵便で萱ね一
It is the mail.
ここには配達員が来れないので
ド口一ンが配達し亡くれ亡ま曹
The post office can no longer deliver here,
so drones like this one bring it instead.
The post office's drones?
郵便局が力` ?
No, they belong to the Hero Association.
いえ ヒ一口一協会力`らの転送で萱
I see.
The public sends these to the heroes,
much like fan letters.
ジ工ノス
一般の人力ヽらヒ一ロ一宛ての一
おそら<
ファンレ夕一のようなもので曹ね
Seriously?
サイタマ本当力ヽ オイオイ
俺宛亡のもあるの力ヽ?
Are there any for me?
TO C-CLASS HERO SAITAMA
ジ工ノスありま萱
There are.
Oh! Let's go in and open them!
サイ夕マ
おつ 早<部屋戻つて開けようぜ
MR. GENOS,
I'VE BEEN A HUGE
FAN OF YOURS SINCE I FIRST
LAID EYES ON YOU! I THINK
YOU ARE A TRUE HERO. I
EVEN JOINED YOUR FAN
CLUB! I'M JUST CRAZY
ABOUT YOU!
TO C-CLASS HERO SAITAMA
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
NO ONE CARES
ABOUT YOU, YOU COWARDLY,
CHEATING BASTARD.
TO C-CLASS HERO SAITAMA
Damn it...
こいつ…
ちよつ と差出人調ベ亡俺が…
I'll find out who sent it.
ヒマな奴がいるな
Here's a guy with free time.
丿ヽツ
All it took was one punch!
男性ー
一発で 仕留めち まつ たぞ一
One punch! Just one!
ワンパンだよ ワンパン!
Is he really C-class?
C級じやないのガよ
He's too strong!
強萱ぎる !
Or maybe...
男そう力`?
The monster wasn't really that tough?
実はあんまり強い怪人じゃ
な力ヽつたんじゃね?
Yeah, but so many heroes went down.
いや でも
色んなヒ一口一が負け亡るぞ
That just means those heroes were weaklings.
んじや 負けたヒ一口一が
もつと弱力ヽつたつてことじゃね?
それは… 確力ヽに今のを見ると
敵が弱く見えたけど…
Maybe...
I suppose the monster didn't
look all that tough when he killed it.
After all, a C-class hero
took it out with a single punch!
そこにいるC級ヒ一口一が
一発で倒しちゃつたんだぜ笑一
What's that say about the heroes it beat?
負けたヒ一口一つ亡 どんだけだよ一
A級と力ヽS級と力ヽつ亡
肩害きだけで一
They may call themselves A-class or S-class,
but their titles don't mean a thing.
ぶっちゃけ大したことないんだな
クククク…
Hey, enough of that.
They risked their lives for us.
おい やめろよ
一応 命張つて<れたんだぜ
命張るだけなら誰でもできるじやん
Risked their lives? Anyone can do that.
But a "hero" has to beat monsters.
怪人倒してこそヒ一口一だろ ?
It all ended well this time, so whatever.
ま 結果的に助力`つた力`ら
いいんだけど
But it's annoying when heroes who are really
just average Joes show up and try to save you.
ああいう一般人と
変わらないヒ一ロ一なん亡一
助けに来られ亡も困惑萱るだけだよね
If you're gonna call yourself a hero, then—
やつぱヒ一口一名乗る力`らには…
Shut your fat mouth!
おい お前 いい加減にしろよ!
何で俺が怒られないと
いけないの?
Why are you getting mad at me?
The Hero Association gets their funds
from our donations, right?
ヒ一口一協会の資金は
みんなの募金が元だろ?
お金払つてる力ヽらには
ちゃんと守つてもらわないと困るよね一
As long as we're paying for it,
they'd better protect us.
The fact of the matter is that bald guy
pretty much took care of it all by himself.
実際 今回はあのハグてる人が
ー人で解決しちゃつたわけだし一
So all the other heroes died for nothing.
他のヒ一口一は
無駄死にだったよね一
時間稼ぎなんて
工夫曹れば誰でもできるしさ一
Anyone can come up with
a way to buy a little time.
In the end, the other heroes
didn't do anything heroic.
他のヒ一口一つ亡 結局
何もヒ一口一らしい活躍し亡なくね?
I said shut up!
男性6 やめろつ亡 !
We were all saved. Just leave it at that.
男性7とに力ヽく助力ヽったんだ
それでいいじゃなぃか
Exactly!
女性 そ うよ
サイ夕マ
あは・・ あつはつはつはつ…
Today's my lucky day!
いや一 ラツキ一だつた一
他のヒ一口一が怪人の体力
奪ってて<れたおかげで一
The other heroes wore the monster down,
so beating it was kid's play!
スゲ一楽に倒せた
丿ヽツ
Good thing I was late.
サイタマ遅れ亡来亡よ力`つた一
俺 何もやつてないのに
手柄 独り占めにできたぜ一
I barely did a thing and now
I get all the credit.
Hey, spread the word, all of you!
あ お前ら
ちゃんと噂まいとけよ!
I'm the one who finished the monster off!
最後に怪人仕留めたのは俺だ力`らな
本当はただ遅刻し亡きただけと力ヽ
バラしたら
I'll beat the snot out of anyone who
says it's only 'cause I got here late!
ぶつ飛ば萱ぞ !
What's he mean?
男性8え? どういうこと?
The monster was already weak?
男性9 萱でに弱つ亡たつてこと力`
Huh?
男性ー。あれえ… ちよつと待てよ
あいつ サイタマだ
Hang on a sec.
That's Saitama!
Saitama?
男性ーーサイ夕マ?
He's the hero from City Z
that everyone calls a cheat.
Z市でインチキ呼ばわりされ亡
話題になってたヒ一口一だよ
What? A cheat?
え? インチキ?
He appeared out of nowhere
and climbed the ranks super-fast.
いきなり出亡き亡 もの曹ごい早さで
順位を上げ亡んだよな
Yeah, pretty fishy.
怪しいよな
Hey, you guys!
壬サイ夕マおい お前ら!
倒れたヒ一口一たちを
ちゃんと看亡やれよ
Look after the fallen heroes, okay?
If they die on me,
死なれたら困るんだよ
how am I gonna cash in on their work?
俺が利用できななるだろ
He is a cheat!
やつぱインチキ力`
Man, that's no fair.
うわ一 ずるいな
So he's just taking the credit?
手柄だけ横取 り 力`よ
男性ー
比ベてみると他のヒ一口一のほうが
ヒ一ロ一らしいな
Compared to him, the other heroes
seem a little more heroic.
Where would we be now if
the other heroes hadn't fought?
男性2怪人を弱らせ亡くれた
ヒ一口一たち力ヾいな力ヽつたら一
今頃 俺たちは…
Yeah, I feel so grateful to them all.
男性ーああ… ヒ一ロ一たちに
心力ヽら感謝だな
Master Saitama...
ジ工ノス サイ夕マ先生一
Is this really what you want?
本当にそれでいいんで萱ね
Hey, it stopped raining.
サイ夕マ お 雨やんだな
If this is the path you choose to walk,
I will not interfere.
ジ工ノス
それが先生の進む道だというなら>一
俺は何もロを出しません一
But in the future,
if you are ever forced into a corner by this,
もし今後 サイ夕マ先生が一
<本当に追い詰められるようなことが
あったら>一
at that moment, I will—
その時こそ 俺が…
サイ夕マ お まだあるじやん
Hey, there's one more.
TO THE HERO SAITAMA:
THANKS!!
Someone's thanking me.
感謝され亡る
何処力ヽで助けられた誰力ヽで曹ね
きつと
It must be someone you saved.
I see.
そつ力`… もうない?
Any left?
あ もうー 通 これは協会力`らで萱
There is one from the Hero Association.
協会 ?
The Association?
Are they firing me?
ク ビの通知力` ?
Well, whatever.
別にいいけど一
ー位?一
ん? 何だ これ C級…
What's this?
I'm Class C rank 1?
CITY Z - HERO ASSOCIATION OFFICE
で` 何で俺は
呼ひ出されたんだ?
So, why'd you call me in?
When you registered with the Hero Registry,
Z支部審査委員蝿
ヒ一口一名簿に登録した時一
協会力`ら手帳を支給されただろう ?
you were given the Association handbook.
Haven't you read it?
Z支部審査委員2
キ三 読んでないの?一
It lists all our rules and regulations.
色んな規約とか丿し一ルが
記載され亡るんだけど
Yeah, I guess I've got it somewhere.
サイ夕マ
探せばどつ力ヽあると思うんだけど
No matter.
Z支部審査委員3
まあ まずは
C級ランキングー位おめでとう
Congratulations on attaining rank 1 in Class C.
Hm?
ん? ああ そつ力`
Oh, I see.
So you guys are the ones
who decide the hero rankings.
アン夕らが決め亡んの力ヽ
ヒ一ロ一の格付け
There are more members
on the review board,
Z支部審査委員3
審査会は大勢の人員で動いているが一
but the four of us here today
will be handling your interview.
今 日 の面接担当 は我々 4 人だ
面接だ ?
Interview?
The top ranking C-class hero is given
the option to be promoted to Class B.
Z支部審査委員3
C級ランキング卜ツプに立つた者には
巳級ラン力一への昇格権が与えられる
However, if you wish to remain
in Class C, that's fine too.
まあ ずつとC級でいたいなら
それでも〇Kだ
How about it, Mr. Saitama?
Z支部審査委員2
どう萱る? サイタマ君一
巳級に上がる力`? _
Do you want to move up?
Although if you do,
you'll be ranked at the very bottom again.
順位はまた最下位になつてしまうが
Either way's fine,
but I guess I'll try moving up.
どつちでもいいけど
せつ力ヽ<だし巳級になつてみる力ヽ
There'll be no more
weekly quotas that way.
週ー 活動の報告もななるんだろ ?
サイ夕マ
それに… ジ工ノス力ヾS級で
俺力ヾいつまでもC級つ亡のもな>
Besides, I can't stick to Class C
forever with Genos in Class S.
I see, so you want a promotion.
そう力` 昇格希望力`
First, we'll need you to answer some questions
and undergo a psychiatric analysis.
では 簡単な質疑応答と
精神分析のテス 卜を し亡も らいま萱
This Saitama...
特別審査委員ー サイ夕マ君…一
He's the one who finished off
the Deep Sea King.
彼力ヽ 例の深海王に
卜ドメをさしたという
What do you think?
特別審査委員 2 どう思う ? 一
Some say he's a fraud...
本当にインチキば力`りなら…
特別審査委員ー
身体能力は体力試験の
総合最高記録という 折り紙つきだがな
He set new overall records in the fitness exam,
so his physical ability is solid.
Well, according to rumors,
he cheated on the exams, too.
いえ 彼はそれ曹らインチキなのではと
囁尊されていま首
Rumors are just rumors.
メガネ職員 噂は噂
No sense in doubting him now.
今さら疑っても
しょう力ヾないのではないでしょう力ヽ
本人が昇格を希望しているんで萱一
The bottom line is, he wants to move up.
Why not let him go for now?
もう少し泳がせ亡み亡はどうで萱 ? _
本物なら巳級でも通用しま萱
If he's for real, he'll make it in Class B.
But if he's a fake, he'll soon regret it.
だ力ヾ もし偽物なら
彼は後悔曹ることになるぞ一
He is entering a cruel and callous world.
過酷な世界に
身を移してしまったことに
その時は その時で萱
We'll cross that bridge when we must.
Promotion to Class B?
アマイマスク 巳級昇格? _
You interrupted my filming for this?
ドラマ撮影中に何力`と思えば
It's not something that needs my attention.
そんなの僕を通さなたつ亡いいよ
This is a decision for the executive committee.
ヒゲ 職員
一応 役員会の取り決めでして
Listen.
いい力`?
I only want input on managing
A-class heroes and above,
僕がロを出させろと言つたのは
あ<まで社会的影響の強い
A級以上のヒ一口一の管理だ
since they have a strong impact on society.
同じ所属 と し亡
As a hero in the same class,
if they're inadequate, it hurts my image too.
お粗末な振る舞いをされると
迷惑だ力ヽらね
Especially this last incident...
特に今回の件なん亡一
It was beyond inadequate. It was appalling.
お粗末を通り越し亡無様だよ
Don't you agree?
そうは思わない力`?
社会的影響といえば
今回 昇格を希望曹るヒ一口一は
Speaking of social impact, the hero now wanting to
move up is the one who finished off the Deep Sea King.
その深海王に
卜ドメをさした男ではありま曹
UNKNOWN HEROES
SNATCH VICTORY
イナズマックス・ステインガ一 はあ…
Why the sour pusses?
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
何しょげた顔してるんだ?
イナズマツクス・ステインガ一 あ ?
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
力ヽわいいお顔が台無しだぞ?
That's no way to show off those cute faces!
You?!
ステインガ一 アン夕は  ?
I thought you were in prison!
イナズマックス
刑務所に戻ったはずじゃ
I escaped just to see you!
ぷりぷりプリズナ一
あなたに会いに脱獄成功!
Now... It's time for your Angel shots!
さあ 工ンジ工ルお注射の時間だ!
イナズマックスうわあ!
スティンガ一ちよちよ… 待つ亡<れ~!
あなたたち ! 治療だぞ~!
You guys! You need your meds!
AN "S-CLASS" FAILURE!
So I'm B-class now...
サイ夕マ今日力`ら巳級力`
やけに時間か力`つちまつたな
Those tests took long enough.
Meh, not like I had to be somewhere.
ま 俺もヒマし亡たけど おつ一
うまそうな匂い
Something smells good...
Welcome.
大将 ラ ツ シヤイ
Assorted oden, please.
おでん盛り合わせ
大将 ハイよ
All right.
Want a drink?
無免ライダ一飲まないの力`?
If you're not drinking,
let me buy you a plate.
無免ライダ一飲まないなら
何力ヽ奢らせてくれ
Why?
なんで?
That.
それ一
協会に行つ亡きたんだろ ?
You were at the Association?
れは昇格祝いだ
」
Let's celebrate your promotion.
サイ夕マ悪いな一
Thanks for giving me a ride.
乗せ亡もらつ亡
降りよう力`?
Should I walk?
N-No... I can handle this much...
い いや… これらい大丈夫だ一
Hey, are you scared?
なあ キ三は怖ないの力` ?
S級のジ工ノスさんに付い亡来亡
はぐれ亡しまつたんだろ?
You got separated from
the S-class hero, Genos, right?
The enemy is threat level Demon,
相手は災害レベル 鬼一
a monster so formidable that even if the Class S and
Class B heroes all ganged up on him, they'd never win.
そもそもC級や巳級が
束になっても一
勝亡る見込みのない強敵だ一
So if you wanna run...
逃げるのなら…
Are you S-class too?
サイ夕マ お前もS級なの力`?
No, I'm C-class.
無免ライダ一
いや 俺はC級だが…一
Laugh if you want to.
笑いたければ笑つ亡れ
I'm not laughing.
笑わねえよ一
It sure is tough making those
weekly quotas for us C-class heroes...
週ー 活動のノ丿しマ キツいもんな
俺たちC級は
フフ"・ 面白い人だな キ三は
You're a funny guy.
I'm Licenseless Rider.
俺は無免ライダ一 `
キ三と同じ ヒ一口一だ
A hero, just like you.
Huh?
Hey! Watch it!
おい 前見ろ 前!一
ああ お前 あん時の
Oh!
You're that guy!
I've been looking for you.
今日はキ三を捜し亡いた一
I couldn't say everything in my letter.
手紙では伝えきれなてね
Oh yeah.
そつ力`一
Maybe a seaweed dish then?
じやあ もず れ
Sir, please serve us your best seaweed dish!
無免ライダ一
ご主人! 彼に 良いもずくを!
Comin' right up.
大将 ハイよ
Come home to me
When my worries keep me awake by the crescent moon
all I can do is think of you with my eyes closed
I want to see you, want to cry, feel the romance
I hope you realize my feelings
I know so well
how hard you work
My beloved, you are so strong, and still I worry
Only I ever see your weakness
I will find you before the stars do
Come to me now
Come home to me
シババワあああ… ああ あああ…
I-It approaches!
来る 来る!
Madame Shibabawa?
シババワ様?
い力ヽ力ヾされました力ヽ?
What's wrong?
怒濤の大災害が押し寄せて…
A violent catastrophe draws near...
Madame Shibabawa! Get a hold of yourself!
シババワ様! お気を確力`に !
This is the end!
終末があああ ! 一
はあ はあ…
ち・ 地球がヤバい !
The Earth is doomed!
Next
Time
Unparalleled
Peril
Eh? What is this place?
深海王 ん ? あれ ? ここは何処 ? _
I am the Deep Sea King!
私は深海王一
今回 誤算があるとしたら
海の戦いじゃな力ヽったところよね一
If I made one misstep,
it was not fighting the battle at sea.
An away game!
いわばアウ工一 ! _
海の中なら負けてないし
むしろ余裕 ! 一
If we'd fought at sea,
it would have turned out differently!
Next time on One-Punch Man episode ten,
では次回 ワンパンマン 第ー。話
『力ヽつ亡ない程の危機』 一
"Unparalleled Peril."
Really? There's something
even more dangerous than me?
へえ一 この私以上に
ヤバいことなん亡 あるの力ヽしら?